He didn't come here to be a hero, but things change.
Battle of the Damned is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Christopher Hatton.
Following a deadly viral outbreak, private military soldier Max Gatling leads a handful
of survivors and a ragtag band of robots against an army of the infected.
Max Gatling, played by Dolph Lundgren.
Reese, played by Matt Doran.
Jude, played by Melanie Zanetti.
Duke, played by David Field.
Lynn, played by Lydia Look.
Broadus, played by Broadus Mattison.
The Damned (Götterdämmerung) (Italian: La caduta degli dei, lit.
'The Fall of the Gods') is a 1969 historical drama film directed and co-written by Luchino Visconti, and starring Dirk Bogarde, Ingrid Thulin, Helmut
Berger, Helmut Griem, Umberto Orsini, Charlotte Rampling, Florinda Bolkan, Reinhard Kolldehoff and Albrecht Schönhals in his final film.
Set in 1930s Germany, the film centers on the Essenbecks, a wealthy industrialist family who have begun doing business with the Nazi Party, and
whose amoral and unstable heir, Martin (played by Berger in his breakthrough role), is embroiled in his family's machinations.
It is loosely based on the German Krupp family of
steel industrialists from Essen.
Principal photography of The Damned took place in locations
throughout Italy, West Germany, and Austria.
The film opened to widespread critical acclaim, but also faced
controversy from ratings boards for its sexual content.
In the United States, the film was given an X rating by the MPAA, which was lowered to
a more marketable R after 12 minutes of offending footage were cut.
Visconti won the Nastro d'Argento for Best Director, and was nominated for a Best
Original Screenplay Oscar with co-writers Nicola Badalucco and Enrico Medioli.
Helmut Berger received a Golden Globe nomination for Most Promising Newcomer.
The film won the Golden Peacock (Best Film) at the 4th
International Film Festival of India.
The film explores themes of rescue mission, zombie, robot, virus.
The tone is thought_provoking.